Grew up in the military, worked in the military.
我在部隊長大 工作 總被派去不同的地方 要求準時報到
Always told where to go, when to be there. I want to see my country on my own terms.
現在我按自己的心意 好好看看這個國家
Motels, cash, fake names, travel light.
住汽車旅館 隨身攜帶現金 用假名 輕裝旅行
You get used to it.
你會習慣的
So far, a run on his prints has been clean, but something could still turn up.
搜索他的指紋沒有發現案底 不過還是應該有所發現的
No driver's license, mortgage, insurance claims.
沒有駕照 抵押貸款 保險索賠
No online profile at all.
根本沒有在線個人資料
The only proof Jack Reacher exists is the fact that he's sitting in that room.
杰克雷徹存在的唯一證據 就是他坐在那個房間里面
Took out a few men in the course of your duties.
在你執行任務的過程中干掉了幾個人
All ruled good kills.
所有都被裁定為有正當理由
Commanded the 110th Special Investigations Unit
曾經領導憲兵隊的110
of the Military Police.
特別調查組
100,000 years ago,
十萬年前
there were people who stayed by the campfire and people who wandered.
就有些人會留在篝火旁 還有些人會去流浪
I'm pretty sure I'm a direct descendant of the wandering type.
我很確定我是流浪族群的直系后代
It's just who I am.
這是我的本性
What am I supposed to do with these?
我該怎么處置這些衣服
Wash them and sell them. You're a thrift store.
洗干凈然后賣掉 你這是家二手店
You buying anything? What I'm wearing.
- 你要買什么東西嗎  - 買我穿的這身
Jeans, T-shirt, jacket, socks, boxers.
牛仔褲 T恤 夾克 襪子 平角褲
$22.
22美元
Yeah, Doug was supposed to take that down a few days ago. It's $22.
嗯 道格幾天前就該 把那個折扣標簽撤掉了 是22美元
If you knew they were supposed to come down, why didn't you do it?
那你為什么不把它撤下來
'Cause it's Doug's job.
因為這是道格的工作
There's an ATM across the street.
街對面有個自動提款機
I'll leave you my passport so you know I'm not running off.
這是我的護照 這樣你就不用擔心我跑單了
Don't care if you do. This job is shit.
你跑了我也不在乎 這工作太垃圾了
Sorry, I have to make another withdrawal.
對不起 我必須再取一筆
Don't turn around. I can help you.
別回頭 我可以幫你
Keep taking out money.
繼續取錢
That minivan to my left... that yours?
我左邊的小面包車 那是你的車
Yes.
是的
Just for clarity, you've been carjacked, right?
我先了解清楚 你被劫車了 對吧
My child is in the back seat. Gun?
- 我的孩子在后座 - 有槍
Yes.
是的
Stay here. This won't take long.
待在這里 用不了太久
Come on...
快啊
Your mom better hurry the fuck up, kid, or this is gonna go bad for both of you.
孩子 你媽最好動作快點 否則你們倆就慘了
Hi. Want to see your mom?
嗨 想見你媽媽嗎
It's okay. It's okay.
沒事了 寶貝
Come here. It's okay. I mean, I'm here. Oh, baby.
親愛的 沒事了 我在這
That guy will be out for a while.
那家伙會昏迷一會兒
Go in the bank, call the cops, give them these.
去銀行報警 把這些給他們
Gun's in the car.
槍在車里
Wait. Who are you?
等等 你是誰
Someone who prefers not getting involved.
一個不想被牽涉進去的人
Here's $30. Need a new jacket.
這是30美元 我需要一件新夾克
What's wrong with the one you just bought?
你剛買的那件怎么了
It has blood on it.
上面沾了血
Can I use your phone?
我能借用你的手機嗎
I just got a message from a friend.
我剛收到朋友發來的消息
"Tammi Cates"?
塔米凱茨
Let me guess. Bank teller, diner waitress, thrift shop cashier?
讓我猜猜 是銀行柜員 餐廳服務員還是二手店收銀員
Third one. I got your message.
第三個 我收到你的消息了
110th. 10-30.
110特別調查組 “10-30”
A distress call.
這是求救信號
Distress call and airfare.
是求救信號以及機票
I need you to come to New York ASAP. Why?
- 我需要你盡快來紐約 - 為什么
Calvin Franz was murdered.
卡爾文弗朗茨被謀殺了
I'll let you know when I land.
我下了飛機會通知你的
Major Reacher.
雷徹少校
Hello, sir.
您好 長官
Just Reacher. I didn't tell you to bring anything.
叫我雷徹就好 我沒讓你帶任何東西
Oh, um, just some office supplies, in case there was any start-up paperwork needed to be done.
只是一些辦公用品 以防萬一要做啟動文書工作
- I hate paperwork. - That's okay,
我討厭文書工作
I don't mind doing any clerical there might be, sir.
我倒是不介意做文書工作 長官
- Reacher. - Uh, r-right. Reacher.
- 叫我雷徹 - 對了 雷徹
Um, I hope you don't mind my asking, what exactly am I doing here?
希望你不介意我這么問 我到底是來干什么的
- Want out already, Franz? - No, sir. Um, Reacher.
- 弗朗茨 你已經想退出了  - 不是的 長官...雷徹
Uh, no. I-I don't. I'm just curious is all.
我沒想退出 我只是很好奇
Saw you a few weeks ago by your barracks.
幾周前 我在你的軍營里見過你
Stopped a couple soldiers from beating the hell of each other over a stolen care package from home.
你當時阻止了幾個士兵 為從家里偷來的護理包打架
Last cookie in the box, actually.
實際上是盒子里的最后一塊餅干
One cookie?
一塊餅干
- Yeah. - Even dumber.
- 是啊 - 那更蠢了
Bottom line, you negotiated a fair settlement,
至少 你談判出了 一個公平的解決方案
cracked a few jokes, de-escalated the conflict.
開了幾個玩笑 緩解了沖突
Got a decent head on you. Might come in handy.
你的腦子轉得挺快 可能會派上用場
Okay, I got to ask,
好吧 我得問問
what the hell kind of unit did Major Reacher put together here, huh?
雷徹少校到底在這里 組建了一支什么樣的隊伍
We got a bean counter from Accounting Services,
我們有從會計部找來的會計
a gas jockey from bulk fuel,
散裝燃料公司的加油站員工
we got Dave Matthews,
我們有音樂才子
Grandpa Moses and, uh, a couple of guys from, uh...
摩西爺爺 還有幾個人 來自...
where y'all from? I've seen you in Requisitions, right?
你們都是從哪兒來的  我在采購部見過你們 對吧
We've got names.
我們有名字
Sanchez and Orozco.
桑切斯和奧羅斯科
Which one's Orozco?
哪個是奧羅斯科
And who are you, besides a guy who talks too much?
除了話癆 你又是什么人
David O'Donnell.
大衛奧唐納
And no offense, Pops, but, uh, why are you here?
無意冒犯 老大爺 但你來這里做什么
Isn't there a CBS drama you're missing?
你是錯過了老年電視劇還是怎么著
Lowrey won the Army Marksmanship competition
勞萊曾六次贏得陸軍
six times, both pistol and rifle class.
手槍和步槍射擊比賽
I've got a rule.
我有個規矩
Plans go to hell soon as first shot's been fired,
一旦打出第一槍 計劃就見鬼去吧
so your first shot better be your best shot.
所以你們的第一槍 最好是打得最準的一槍
I'm the only non-Marine to win the USMC 1,000 Yard Invitational,
我是唯一一個贏得 千碼邀請賽的非海軍隊員
and I still know Lowrey gives us our best first shot.
而且我都知道勞萊 是我們最厲害的“第一槍”
You think this unit's gonna come under a lot of fire?
你覺得這支隊伍會遭受槍擊
Maybe.
說不準
Then why'd you grab a bunch of people with no police experience, Major Reacher?
那你為什么要找 沒有警察經歷的人來 雷徹少校
- Reacher. - Reacher.
- 叫我雷徹 - 叫他雷徹
Sorry.
對不起
Army wanted a unit for particularly complex matters when they arose.
軍隊需要一支 專門處理復雜事務的隊伍
To do that, I need special investigators, not generic MPs.
為此 我需要特別調查員 不是一般的憲兵
If we're so special, why did they stick us in this dump?
如果我們那么特別 那為什么給我們的辦公室這么垃圾
I mean, what is up with this place?
這地方是怎么回事
Few years ago, Uncle Sam made an auction bid for some land down the road.
幾年前 山姆大叔 出價購買了這條街上的一些土地
Entered the address backwards
地址輸反了
and became the proud owners of this building and the contents
就成了這棟建筑的驕傲的主人 而且還成了現已結業的
of the now-defunct Callahan Insurance Agency.
卡拉翰保險公司的所有人
But you're right. Place could work a little better.
但你說得對 辦公地點可以更好一點
Straighten up these boxes,
整理好這些箱子
move these old tanker desks to the middle of the room.
把這些舊桌子移到房間中間
Let's go.
動手吧
You don't have to call me "Major,"
你們不必叫我少校
but you do have to move your ass when I say so. Get to it.
但我讓你們行動時 你們必須動起來 開始吧
Go backwards.
向后退
Okay, you want me to go backwards?
你想讓我向后退
- I'm going backwards. - Go back.
- 我要向后退 - 向后退
Lift with your legs, man! No one lifts with their legs.
- 腿用力 抬起來 - 沒人用腿抬
On three. One, two, three, go.
數到三 一 二 三 抬
You're doing it wrong.
你這么抬不對
I'm doing it exactly how you told me to.
我是按你說的做的
You think we're actually gonna be able to work together?
你覺得我們真能一起工作
No idea.
我不知道
But I could use a beer.
但我可以請大家喝酒
Tell them I'm buying.
跟他們說我買單
Reacher.
雷徹
Neagley.
內格利
Thanks for ordering. Still steam coming off the cup.
謝謝你點餐 杯子里還冒著熱氣
Tracked the plane online, saw it landed early,
我在網上追蹤了航班信息 看到它提前落地了
you don't check bags and I adjusted for traffic.
你不托運行李 我算了通勤時間
Had the coffee poured 90 seconds ago.
90秒前倒的咖啡
Food's been there three minutes.
食物已經上桌三分鐘了
Appreciated.
非常感謝
Where'd you get this?
這是從哪兒弄到的
I'm a PI. I can get things.
我是私家偵探 能搜集到這些東西
Been a minute since Margrave.
距離馬格雷夫一別有些時日了
Been two years, seven months, 19 days.
是兩年七個月19天
You look good.
你氣色不錯
I look the same.
我看起來沒變化
You looked good two years, seven months, 19 days ago,
跟兩年七個月19天前一樣好
so, yeah. You look the same.
所以你看起來也一樣
You look... road-worn.
你看起來鞍馬勞頓
Yep.
是啊
So, Franz. Give me the Cliff Notes.
那么 弗朗茨 給我講講大體情況
Went missing after leaving his home in Brooklyn about a week or so ago.
大約一周前 他離家后失蹤了
Body was found in the Catskill Mountains.
尸體被發現于卡茲奇山
Whole force up there is, like, 20 cops.
整個警察局有20名警察
And since Franz disappeared in the city, NYPD's taking the lead.
弗朗茨在城里失蹤后 紐約市警察局開始牽頭調查
How'd you find out? Got a call from Angela.
- 你是怎么知道的  - 安吉拉給我打了電話
Franzy's widow.  Franz was married?
- 弗朗茨的遺孀 - 弗朗茨結婚了
Yeah. Fun wedding. Chocolate fountain.
是啊 很有趣的婚禮 還有巧克力噴泉
He had a son, too.
他還有個兒子
What? Life moves on when you're away, big fella.
怎么了 大塊頭 你不在的時候 生活還在繼續
What else?
還有什么消息
Franz left me a few messages in the days before his disappearance.
他失蹤前幾天給我留了幾條信息
Said he wanted to bounce some stuff off of me about a case he was chasing down.
想從我這里了解一些 他正在追查的案件的信息
I was so tied up with my own work, I kept meaning to get back to him, but...
我當時忙著做自己的工作 我一直想回去找他來著
before I could, Angela reached out and told me he'd been murdered.
但在我找他之前 安吉拉聯系我 說他被殺了
It's not your fault.
這不是你的錯
- I know. - He wasn't just murdered.
- 我知道 - 他不僅僅是被謀殺
He was tortured.
還受到了折磨
Nothing but mucus in his stomach. Dehydrated. No food, no water.
他的胃里只有粘液 脫水了 沒有食物 沒有水
Chucked out of a plane.
他被扔出了飛機
They didn't throw him from a plane.
他們不可能是把他扔下飛機的
He was found in the middle of nowhere with injuries
他的尸體被發現于荒無人煙的地方
consistent with a fall from 3,000 feet.
受傷情況跟從一公里的高處 墜落的傷口相吻合
An airplane has a stall speed of what? 80 miles an hour? 100, tops?
飛機的失速速度是多少來著  每小時130公里 最高160公里
They would've shoved him out of the door's plane horizontally into the slipstream.
他們會垂直把他扔到氣流中
He'd bang into the wing or tail.
他會撞到機翼或機尾
There'd be perimortem injuries and there aren't.
那樣會造成死前傷口 但他身上沒有
He was thrown from a helicopter.
他是被從直升機上扔下來的
His broken legs weren't from the fall, anyway. Because?
- 他的腿骨折不是墜地造成的 - 此話怎講
Look at his blood work.
看他的血液檢查結果
Full of free histamines. Massive pain reaction.
充滿了游離組胺 這反映出了劇烈的疼痛反應
You don't get these kind of levels from injuries sustained at the time of death.
直到死前 游離組胺的含量都極高
Broken legs were a few days old.
斷腿是幾天前的事
That's why ferrous oxide powder was found in his pants fabric.
因此 在他褲子的布料中 發現了氧化亞鐵粉
He was hit with a rusty iron bar.
他曾被一根生銹的鐵棒擊中
Must've hurt like hell.
一定疼死了
Yep. He was tortured for either revenge or information.
是啊 他要么是因為報復而被折磨 要么是因為情報
When they were done with him, they dumped him from the sky to avoid ballistics.
兇手得手以后 把他從空中丟出 避免了使用槍支
Couple of college kids wandered off their hiking trail, saw the body.
幾個大學生在徒步的時候 發現了尸體
If not for them, who knows when he would've been found?
否則誰知道他什么時候才會被發現
So, next steps?
那么 接下來呢
If he was calling you for help, he may have been trying to get in touch with the rest of the unit.
如果他給你打過電話 那他可能也給隊里其他人打過
Probably failed.
大概是失敗了
I called O'Donnell, Dixon, Sanchez and Orozco.
我給奧唐納 迪克森 桑切斯和奧羅斯科打了電話
No one's answering.
都沒人接
No listed number for Swan. Even my office can't find it.
斯旺沒有登記電話號碼 連我的辦公室都找不到他的電話
Always a private guy. What about Lowrey?
他總是非常注重隱私 勞萊呢
Killed two years ago in a car accident in Montana.
他兩年前死于蒙大拿的一場車禍
Funeral was sad, but... it was good to see the gang again.
葬禮非常傷感 但很高興再次見到這伙人
Guess life ends when you're away, too.
我猜你不在的時候 有些人也走向了終點
Franz's wedding, Lowrey's funeral. No one told me.
弗朗茨的婚禮 勞萊的葬禮 全都沒人告訴我
No phone, no address.
沒有電話 沒有地址
You could've sent me an emergency ATM message like today.
你本來可以像今天一樣 給我發一條緊急取款機信息
First off, I just thought of that.
首先 我剛想到這個方法
Second, it wasn't really an emergency.
其次 那也不是緊急情況
The emergency was the moment the pickup hit Lowrey.
緊急的是卡車撞上勞萊的那一刻
And be honest, would you really have travelled all the way to Montana
而且說實話 你真的愿意 大老遠地從德州或緬因州
from Texas or Maine or wherever you were at the time
或你當時所在的地方趕到蒙大拿
just to look at a body in a box?
就為了看一眼盒子里的尸體
No.
不愿意
So I'll ask again. Next steps?
那我再問一次 接下來呢
You really want to let some other cops handle our dead friend's case?
你真的想讓其他警察 去處理我們死去的朋友的案子
That's what I thought.
我也這么想
Let's go see Franzy's widow.
我們去見見弗朗茨的遺孀吧
She just met up with the big one.
她剛跟大塊頭見了面
You've reached David O'Donnell. I'm not around;
我是大衛奧唐納 我現在不在
leave a message. I'll call you back.
請留言 我會回電
O'Donnell. This is Reacher with another 10-30.
奧唐納 我是雷徹 現在急需幫忙
Neagley and I are staying at the Vale Hotel in Brooklyn.
內格利和我住在布魯克林的瓦爾酒店
Get off your ass and call us back.
快行動 給我們回電
So, we can't call Swan.
我們沒法給斯旺打電話
O'Donnell, Sanchez and Orozco still don't answer.
奧唐納 桑切斯和奧羅斯科 還是不接電話
And the receptionist at Dixon's office says
迪克森辦公室的接待員
she can't say where Dixon is or when she'll return.
說她不知道她在哪兒 也不知道她何時回來
Probably an undercover job.
可能是在做臥底工作
Maybe.
也許吧
Or maybe they're all in trouble, too.
也許他們也遇到麻煩了
Mikey. Go find your crayons and do some coloring time, okay?
米奇 去拿你的蠟筆 玩填色游戲 好嗎
Please sit.
請坐
Sorry it took me so long to disengage.
抱歉我過了這么久才脫身
It's just hard to get my sister off the phone.
讓我姐姐掛斷電話很難
She calls every hour. My own personal suicide watch.
她每小時打一次電話 是我的個人自殺督查表
Sorry. That was, uh, morbid. I shouldn't have said that.
抱歉 那是種病 我不應該說那話
After what you've been through, you can say whatever you want.
你經歷了那些事 想說什么都行
Can't believe how much your son looks like Franzy.
你的兒子竟然長得那么像弗朗茨
I called him Franzy, too.
我也叫他弗朗茨
Which one of you gave him that name again? I forgot.
是你們中的哪個 給他起的名字來著 我忘了
O'Donnell.
奧唐納
Right. David O'Donnell.
對 大衛奧唐納
And he used to call you The Big Guy.
他曾經叫你“大塊頭”
My God, did Calvin ever tell me stories about you all.
我的天啊 卡爾文 給我講過你們所有人的故事
I know he loved me and Mikey more than anything,
我知道他愛我和米奇勝過一切
but from the way he talked, I don't think he ever ad any more fun
但從他說話的方式來看 我覺得他更享受
than his years spent with the 110th.
他在110組里度過的時光
I don't know about that. Ever since you guys got together,
這可說不準 自從你們在一起后
whenever I talked to him, he seemed joyful.
每當我跟他聊天時 他看上去都很高興
Happier than I ever knew him.
比我認識的他更加高興
Thank you f-for saying that.
謝謝你這么說
I know the police have already asked you a million questions,
我知道警方已經問過你一大堆問題了
but do you think you could walk us through the time line?
但你能講講時間線嗎
Sure.
當然
I was away with Mikey in Provo,
我當時跟米奇在普洛佛
helping my sister with our mom.
幫姐姐照顧我們的媽媽
Early-onset dementia.
她有早發性癡呆
I tried Calvin for a few days, and no return calls.
我試著聯系了卡爾文幾天 但他沒有回電話
It's not like him, so I started to worry.
這不像他的作風 所以我開始擔心
Called NYPD,
我給紐約警局打電話
they just said he could've been out on a case because he was a PI
他們說他可能是出去查案子了 因為他是一名私家偵探
or maybe he was out partying because his wife and kid were out of town.
或者他可能出去參加派對了 因為他的老婆和孩子不在
Do you think that's what he was doing? Out partying with the wrong crowd?
你覺得他是去做那事了嗎  出去跟損友聚會
Cal would call if he was gonna be ten minutes late for dinner.
卡爾文連晚餐遲到十分鐘 都會給我打電話
And he didn't party with anybody.
他不會跟別人參加派對
So I got so worried, I came back early to find our home ransacked.
所以我很擔心 我提早回來 發現我們家被搜了個遍
Nothing was taken.
什么都沒被拿走
The cops have no idea who did it.
警察不知道是誰干的
Were you aware of any cases Franz may have been working on?
你知道他可能在查什么案子嗎
He never brought work home.
他從不把工作帶回家
He said when he was here,
他說他在家的時候
he wanted to be 100% present for me,
希望把百分之百的心思花在我
and Mikey.
還有米奇身上
I'm sorry.
對不起
I want to help. It's just so hard.
我想幫忙 這太難了
Every day hurts.
每天都很痛苦
Just a few more questions. Promise.
再問幾個問題 我保證就幾個
Okay.
好的
What was his client base like?
他的客戶群是什么樣的
Wall Street types. CEOs, the hedge fund crowd.
華爾街那種 首席執行官 對沖基金人群
Any of them particularly rough? Causing him problems? Stressing him out?
有特別難搞的客戶嗎  給他帶來麻煩的 讓他壓力很大的
No. Not at all. Once Mikey came along,
一個都沒有
he stopped doing the dangerous jobs.
米奇一出生 他就不再做危險的工作了
Or so I thought.
現在看來并非如此
Were any other members of the 110th working with him?
他跟110組的其他人有合作嗎
I don't know. Maybe there's something in his office.
我不知道 也許他的辦公室里有什么線索
Sign on the door is Three Rivers Consulting and Associates.
門上的招牌是三河咨詢公司
It's 103 Flatbush. It was trashed, too.
在弗拉特布什103號
The cops couldn't find anything there,
辦公室也被毀了 警察在那里一無所獲
but from what Franzy always told me,
但弗朗茨總是告訴我
the Special Investigators weren't any old group of cops.
特別調查員不是普通的警察
You do not mess with the Special Investigators.
不要惹特別調查員
Your daddy teach you that?
你爸教你的
Do you want to know how your dad became a Special Investigator?
你想知道你爸 是怎么成為特別調查員的嗎
He stopped a fight between two huge soldiers
他阻止了兩個大塊頭士兵之間的打斗
because one of them thought the other had stolen
因為其中一人以為
the last homemade cookie sent to him from his mom.
另一個人偷了他媽媽給他的 餅干盒里的最后一塊自制餅干
Your dad got them to shake hands and be friends again.
你爸爸讓他們握手言和 再次成為朋友
And this guy, right here,
而這里的這個人
he wanted your dad to be part of the 110th because...
他想讓你爸爸加入110組 因為...
...he saw a man who stayed cool when things got heated.
他發現了一個能在情況激烈時 保持冷靜的人
That's how we became friends with your dad.
就這樣 我們跟你爸成了朋友
Okay.
好的
You know Franz ate the cookie.
你知道是弗朗茨吃了餅干
- Thought it was for everyone? - Yup.
- 以為人人有份  - 是啊
I'm pretty sure that black sedan halfway down the street
我很確定街上那輛黑色轎車
was outside the diner, too.
剛才我們吃飯時也在餐館外
There's a black sedan on every street in America. Get in.
美國每條街道上都有黑色轎車 上車
Did the manager talk? Nah, I paid off the concierge.
- 經理說話了嗎  - 沒 我買通了門房
He ID'd Neagley as checking in under the name Sarah Conner
他指認內格利以莎拉寇娜的名字 登記入住
and, uh, paying for an adjoining room using the name Starlin Castro.
并且用史達林卡斯楚的名字 支付了隔壁房間的費用
That must be for the Hulk.
一定是給大塊頭付的房費
Starlin Castro played for the Yankees, six or seven years ago.
六七年前 史達林卡斯楚 曾效力于洋基隊
And who's Sarah Conner?
對 莎拉寇娜是誰
I don't give a shit.
我不在乎
Just keep an eye on that hotel... and them.
盯緊那家酒店還有他們
Copy that.
收到
Pretty modest for a guy with Wall Street business.
對于跟華爾街生意人士 打交道的人來說 這很低調
Unpretentious.
樸實無華
Close to home so he can spend more time with his family.
離家近 這樣他能多陪陪家人
Exact kind of place Franzy would choose.
正是弗朗茨會選的地方
Angela wasn't kidding when she said trashed.
安吉拉說辦公室“被毀了” 她沒開玩笑
They probably didn't find anything.
他們可能什么都沒發現
How do you know that?
你怎么知道
You don't go to this length if you found what you needed right away.
如果你能馬上找到需要的東西 就不會這么大費周章
And they left pissed.
他們離開時很生氣
They weren't looking for anything behind this glass window, but they put that phone through it.
他們沒搜窗戶后面 卻用電話砸穿了
That's an act of frustration by someone who didn't find what they wanted.
這是人沒發現自己想找的東西時 沮喪的表現
Whatever they wanted was small.
他們想要的東西很小
You don't snap chair legs in half to see
若不是要找能塞進椅子腿的東西
if they've been hollowed out unless you're looking for something that can fit in there.
你不會折斷椅子腿 來看它是否是空心的
Hey.
嘿
Check this out.
看看這個
Seems like yesterday.
仿佛是昨天的事
Keychain?
鑰匙鏈
Franz was sharp, right?
弗朗茨很機警 對吧
Very sharp.
非常機警
So if he was dealing with something that could get him killed,
如果他要處理 可能會讓自己喪命的東西
he'd have to put it in a place that was very secure, but readily available.
他必須把它放在一個 安全但很容易獲取的地方
Somewhere in plain sight that we see every day,
我們每天都能見到
but a place no one would suspect.
但又不會引起別人懷疑的地方
Okay.
對
So what's a place that's readily available
所以什么地方是唾手可得
that we entrust every day with very important items?
可以將重要物品托付在那里的呢
This is a mailbox key.
這是郵箱鑰匙
I ever tell you you're smart, Neagley?
我有沒有說過你很聰明 內格利
Not nearly enough.
還遠遠不夠
Shit. It's after 5:00.
見鬼 已經五點過了
10,000 combinations if it's a four-number code.
如果是四位數密碼 那有一萬種組合
- No point in trying. - Good.
- 嘗試沒有意義 - 很好
Hate guessing passwords.
我很討厭猜密碼
We'll have to come back tomorrow.
我們得明天再來
So, what do we do now?
那我們現在干什么
Gin.
金
I don't even know why I play.
我都不知道我為什么要玩
'Cause you hold out hope you'll beat me. I won a few hands.
- 因為你抱著贏我的希望 - 我贏了幾手牌
If you let me win, I'm gonna be pissed.
如果你放水 我會生氣的
I don't let you win. I pace myself.
我不會放水 我會慢慢調整我的節奏
Not in your professional life.
你的職業生涯可不是這樣的
Don't follow.
我沒聽懂
Rental car's a Range Rover, killer hotel rooms,
租的車是輛路虎攬勝 非常棒的酒店房間
sent me airfare like it was nothing.
給我寄了機票 好像票不值錢一樣
You're doing well.
你事業很成功
Clearly not pacing yourself in your professional life.
很明顯在你的職業生涯中 你沒慢慢調整節奏
Not to brag, but the term "wunderkind" has been tossed around the office.
不是我吹牛 “少年得志” 這個詞已經在我辦公室傳開了
Two promotions in the past two years.
在過去的兩年里 我兩次升職
They're opening a satellite office in St. Louis.
他們要在圣路易斯開一家分公司
Offered me director if I wanted it.
他們讓我去當負責人
But I like being in the field too much.
但我太喜歡出外勤了
Doing what?
出外勤做什么
Mostly investigative work for high-income individuals.
主要是給高收入人群
Government entities, family offices, that kind of thing.
政府機構 家族企業之類的 做調查工作
Once in a while we do a pro bono case.
我們偶爾會接一些無償的案子
Missing kids, stolen artwork...
找失蹤的孩子 被盜的藝術品
So, it's not just about the money.
所以這不僅僅是為了賺錢
It feels good.
感覺很不錯
What about you?
你呢
Saw a minor league game in Sioux Falls a while back.
不久前在蘇福爾斯看了一場 小職業球隊聯盟的比賽
Riveting.
真引人入勝
See it with anyone else?
跟其他人一起看的
No.
不是
Did you, uh... talk to anyone at the game?
你在看比賽時跟任何人說話了嗎
I ordered a beer.
我點了杯啤酒
Okay.
好吧
Speaking of talking to people,
說到跟人說話
when you went out to get gas, I tried everyone again.
你出去加油的時候 我又試著給大家打了電話
Radio silence.
無線電靜默
Who'd you call the most?
你給誰打得最多
Sanchez? Orozco? O'Donnell?
桑切斯 奧羅斯科 奧唐納
Or... Dixon?
還是迪克森
She has an answering service.
她有接聽應答服務
Instead of leaving a voice mail, there's someone to actually talk to.
跟語音信箱不同 有人可以說話
Right. 'Cause we just established how much you like talking to people.
對 因為我們剛發現 你有多喜歡跟人聊天
Shut up.
別說了
It's okay.
沒關系
It was always obvious you guys had a thing for each other.
很明顯你們倆對彼此都有好感
Did you ever sleep together?
你們睡過了嗎
No.
沒
Why not? Wouldn't have been appropriate.
- 為什么  - 那樣不合適
You were the same rank.
你們是同一級別的
I ran the team.
我負責管理團隊
Not appropriate.
不合適
But you found her attractive.
但你覺得她很有魅力
- Who wouldn't? - Me.
- 這不是有目共睹的事嗎  - 我就不覺得
I don't find anyone attractive.
我沒發現任何有魅力的人
Gin.
金
I'm going to bed.
我要去睡覺了
I'll pay you back for the room and flight and everything.
我會把房費 機票錢 還有所有費用都還給你
I get my pension deposit in about a week.
大約一周后我就能收到養老金了
Not necessary.
不需要
I wouldn't have my career if I hadn't matriculated at the School of Reacher.
如果我沒被“雷徹學院”錄取的話 就不會有現在的事業
Consider it past-due tuition.
就當是支付我拖欠的學費吧
Something tells me you would've figured it out without me.
沒有我你也能建立一番事業
Besides, it's a little weird having my Master Sergeant carrying my tab.
再說了 讓我的軍士長 替我付錢也很奇怪
I'll get us square.
我會還你的
- Night, Neagley. - Night, Reacher.
- 晚安 內格利 - 晚安 雷徹
For you. Here you go.
給您 這是給您的
Enjoy. Thank you.
- 請慢用 - 謝謝
Well, here's to a lively bunch.
好吧 敬一群活潑的人
Should've brought your banjo.
你應該把你的班卓琴拿來
Well, I think after this round, I'm gonna head back to Accounting.
等喝完這一輪 我要回會計部了
Still have some paperwork I need to finish.
我還得完成一些文書工作
But we just got here.
但我們剛到這里
I know.
我知道
If you don't mind me asking, who directed you to field this team, sir?
如果您不介意我問的話 是誰派您來帶這個小組的 長官
I don't mind you asking. I do mind you calling me "sir."
我不介意你問 但我介意你叫我“長官”
You outrank me.
您的級別比我高
You're a Master Sergeant. Almost everyone outranks you.
你是軍士長 幾乎每個人的級別都比你高
You're not supposed to be drinking in uniform.
你們不應該穿著制服喝酒
We're not drinking.
我們沒喝酒
We were drinking. Then you interrupted us.
我們之前在喝酒 但然后你打斷了我們
She doesn't belong here.
她不屬于這里
It's the Army. Do any of us really belong here?
這里是軍隊 我們中有人屬于這里嗎
You some kind of smart guy? Smarter than you.
- 你算是個聰明人吧  - 比你聰明
I'm also a man with a rule.
我也是個有規矩的人
People leave me and my pals alone, I leave them alone.
人不犯我 我不犯人
They don't, I don't.
人若犯我 我必犯人
I thought his rule was plans go to hell when the first shot's fired.
我以為他的規矩是“一旦 打出第一槍 計劃就見鬼去吧”
It's an officers' club. No enlisted.
這是軍官俱樂部 不是給現役軍人的
How about I just finish my beer and I'll be on my way, okay, sir?
我喝完啤酒就走 好嗎 長官
How about you be quiet? There are adults are talking.
你安靜點吧 大人在說話呢
Now it's either she leaves, or we drag you all out by your asses.
現在 要么她離開 要么我們把你們全都拽出去
I'm providing you an opening because I promised my mother
我給你個機會 因為我答應了我媽
I'd give dumb guys like you a chance to walk away.
會給像你這樣的蠢貨一個脫身的機會
We got 12.
我們有12個人
You got nine.
你有九個
Well, that's a shame.
太可惜了
You're at least three short.
你再叫三個人來才有可能贏
? Oh, don't give us none of your aggravation ?
不要挑釁我們
? We had it with your discipline ?
我們受夠了你的紀律
? Saturday night's all right for fighting...
周六的夜晚...
I thought I was done when that guy got me in a headlock.
他鎖我的頭時 我以為我完了
- Owe you one, brother. - Yeah, brother.
- 欠你一個人情 兄弟  - 是啊 兄弟
Here, give me some more ice, call it even.
再給我拿點冰 我們就扯平了
All right, hot dogs are up in five.
好的 熱狗五分鐘后上桌
? Gonna set this dance alight ?
點燃這支舞
? 'Cause Saturday night's the night I like ?
因為周六的夜晚是我最愛的夜晚
? Saturday night's all right, all right,
周六的夜晚沒問題
all right ?
沒問題
? Saturday, Saturday, Saturday, Saturday...
周六...
Fresh one?
再來一瓶
? Saturday, Saturday, Saturday ?
周六的夜晚沒問題
Cheers.
干杯
? Saturday, Saturday,
- 周六  - 周六
Saturday, Saturday...
周六...
You know, uh, I shouldn't've been at the officers' club.
我不應該去軍官俱樂部的
Saturday
周六
I know.
我知道
Then why get into a fight over it?
那為什么要為這事打架
He didn't ask nicely.
他語氣不善
? Saturday, Saturday, Saturday...
周六
You and I are gonna be pals, aren't we, Reacher?
你和我會成為朋友的 不是嗎 雷徹
Already are, Neagley.
已經是朋友了 內格利
Hungry?
餓嗎
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
嘿
Real quick.
我就說一句
Tonight, the boys of the 91st learned a very important lesson.
91團的男孩們今晚 學到了一個非常重要的教訓
And what did they learn?
他們學到了什么
That you do not mess with the Special Investigators!
不要惹特別調查員
You knew that was gonna happen tonight.
你知道今晚會發生這事
I knew the 91st like to drink on Thursday nights.
我知道91團的人喜歡周四晚上喝酒
And that they're sticklers for the rules.
而且他們墨守成規
And that they're assholes.
而且他們還是混蛋
But now... I know they can all work together.
但現在 我知道他們能一起工作
Photo op to commemorate our first day as a unit.
合影留念 我們作為一個小組的第一天吧
You. Fire.
你 去火邊
- Go. - Okay.
- 好的 - 去吧
How about I just take it? Ah, no, man, I got it.
- 我來照吧  - 我能處理 伙計
No. No, you're not getting out of it that easy. Come on. Come on.
不行 你不能逃避照相 快來
I got this.
我能處理
Okay, guys, four seconds.
好的 各位 四秒鐘
Whoa, take it easy on your osteoporosis. Ah, kiss my ass, young blood.
- 小心你的骨質疏松 - 去你的 年輕人
Okay, night's still young, Swan.
好吧 夜色還早 斯旺
Get back to strumming, baby.
重新開始彈吉他吧 寶貝
"Free Bird"!
《自由鳥》
Hell no.
我才不干
No Skynyrd, no Zeppelin, no Hendrix, no Who.
不彈斯金納德 齊柏林 亨德里克斯和誰人樂隊的歌
I like my music lighter.
我喜歡輕一點的音樂
But never fear, after I take a leak,
但不要害怕 我去撒個尿
you're about to get a little taste of "Crocodile Rock."
然后你們就能欣賞《鱷魚搖滾》
- Can't wait, can't wait. - Hey, Reacher.
- 迫不及待了  - 嘿 雷徹
They tossed me from a helicopter, Reacher.
他們把我從直升機上扔了下去 雷徹
What are you gonna do about it?
你要怎么做
Welcome to Los Angeles International Airport.
歡迎來到洛杉磯國際機場
Passengers, please have passports ready...
乘客們 請準備好護照...
Reason for your visit, Mr. Mount?
芒特先生 您來訪的原因是什么
Oh, Adrian, please. Um, I'm here to sightsee.
請叫我阿德里安 我是來觀光的
Universal Studios, Walk of Fame, Mann's Chinese.
要去環球影城 星光大道 中國戲院
You know, I'm a bit of an Old Hollywood fanatic.
我是個好萊塢狂熱愛好者
Anything to declare?
有需要申報的東西嗎
I have nothing to declare.
我沒有需要申報的
Enjoy your stay, sir.
祝您旅途愉快 先生
Okay, thanks.
好的 謝謝
We'll keep you posted.
我們會跟你保持聯系
Angela has no idea which PO Box belonged to Calvin
安吉拉不知道 哪個郵政郵箱是卡爾文的
and the post office won't give her that information until the estate has been settled
在遺產處理完畢前 郵局不會告訴她
because the box was in his company's name.
因為郵箱是落在他公司的名義下的
Should we check his office again for mail?
我們應該去他辦公室看看郵箱嗎
We were thorough. Nothing in there with a box number on it.
我們搜得很徹底了 那兒沒有寫著郵箱號碼的東西
We can't just go in there and start trying boxes.
我們不能就這樣進去試郵箱
They'll call the cops and we'll wind up with federal mail tampering charges.
他們會報警 而我們會被指控篡改郵件
Then let's think this through.
我們要全面考慮
Like 89% of the world, Franz is right-handed,
跟世界上89%的人一樣 弗朗茨是右撇子
so he probably asked for a box on the right when you enter.
所以他可能會要一個進門右邊的郵箱
Humans favor their dominant side.
人們喜歡自己更順手的一邊
He gets public records sent to him,
他會收到發給他的公共記錄 監控照片
surveillance photos, so he's gonna need one of the big boxes.
所以他需要一個大號的箱子
I'll start with them, see which one's packed with mail
我會從這些信息開始查
since Franz hasn't made a pickup in a while.
看看哪個箱子里面裝滿了郵件 因為他有段時間沒拿了
I just need a distraction.
我只需要你分散他人注意力
Copy that.
收到
Hey, how goes it... Albert?
嘿 你還好嗎 艾伯特
I am a hard-core philatelist
我是個鐵桿集郵迷
and I have been fully aflutter about this new batch of stamps
最近發行的這批郵票
that were recently issued...
讓我非常激動
Which run?
哪個系列的郵票
We've got, uh, Desert Flowers, uh, State Birds and the World of Anime.
我們有沙漠之花 州鳥和動漫世界
All of 'em.
全部都很感興趣
I've got a bunch of Susan Bs jingling in my pocket and I'm ready to spend 'em.
我口袋里有蘇珊硬幣 我準備好花掉這些錢了
Um, okay.
好的
There's at least two dozen of these, uh, cartoons.
至少有兩打這樣的卡通
If you're not familiar with anime, I believe it's Japanese.
不知道你熟不熟悉動漫 我覺得是日本的
You don't say.
好家伙
Oh, and uh... the State Birds are spectacular.
州鳥非常驚人
But never gonna get 50 different species.
但永遠都集不齊五十種
The Western Meadowlark represents six different states.
西部草地鷚代表了六個不同的州
Excuse me. Excuse me. Can I get to my box?
不好意思 能讓我開我的郵箱嗎
Yeah, sure.
當然可以
Sir, is that your key?
先生 那是你的鑰匙嗎
Yeah, I just... can't remember which box is mine.
是的 我只是想不起來 哪個箱子是我的了
Sir, this man is using a key that isn't his.
先生 這個人在用不屬于他的鑰匙
- What are you, the mail police? - Sir, can I help you?
- 你是郵政警察嗎  - 需要幫忙嗎
Could you show me the Flowers, Al?
- 之前郵件被偷過 - 能給我看看花的嗎
Sir. All good here.
- 先生  - 這里一切安好
No, sir, I'm gonna need some ID that ties you to that box.
不 我需要您的身份證件 確保您是那個箱子的主人
You know what? I'll take all of them. How about that?
我全都要 怎么樣
Here we go.
好了
No problem. Just got my boxes confused.
沒事 我只是忘了是哪個箱子了
You know what, Al? I think I'll pass.
你知道怎么著 艾爾 算了吧
What do we got?
都是什么東西
Bills, solicitations...
賬單 請求
Potential.
潛在線索
Looks like your post office hunch worked.
看來你的“郵局直覺”是對的
I ever tell you you're smart, Neagley?
我說過你很聰明嗎 內格利
Not nearly enough. We need to see what's on this.
- 還遠遠不夠 - 我們得看看這里面有什么
Damn it. My laptop has a different port.
該死 我的筆記本的端口不同
I got to go pick up an adapter.
我得去拿個適配器
Do me a favor. Order up a ride on one of those phone app things.
幫我個忙 用手機軟件叫輛出租車
I need to borrow your car.
我得借用你的車
You know Franz was killed over this hard drive
你知道是這個U盤害死弗朗茨的
and now you want to go get a gun.
現在你想去拿把槍
Yup.
是的
But first... I need to go to church.
但首先 我需要去教堂
Excuse me.
打擾一下
I was wondering if I could ask for some help.
我想知道我能否尋求幫助
Well, that is what we give here.
我們就是給人提供幫助的
I'm looking for my cousin.
我在找我的表弟
He has a really bad drug problem
他有很嚴重的吸毒問題
and a family friend said they saw him living on the street around here.
一個朋友說看見他住在附近的街道上
I'm sorry to hear that. Well, thank you.
- 很遺憾聽到這個消息 - 謝謝
I promised my aunt I wouldn't come back home without her son.
我答應過姑姑 不帶上她兒子就不回家
I don't know where to even begin looking.
我甚至都不知道從哪里開始找
And I thought maybe the church has a support group or something, and... through that,
我想也許教堂有個支持小組之類的
maybe you'd have some idea where Jimmy was scoring?
也許可以通過這種小組 了解吉米在哪里買的毒品
The devil did his best work when he created that poison, didn't he?
惡魔創造那種毒藥的時候 已經盡了全力 不是嗎
Sure did.
確實
Almost everyone who comes in to our outreach program
幾乎每個參加我們外展計劃的人
gets their fix from the same place:
都是從同一個地方得到“慰藉”的
Dumont, just east of Rockaway.
那就是洛克威以東的杜蒙特
But you've got to have a death wish to walk in there alone, son.
但你一個人過去 簡直是自尋死路 孩子
I'll be fine, Father.
我會沒事的 神父
I have righteousness on my side.
正義在我這邊
Little extra taste?
再多一點
I'll get you back tomorrow?
我明天會給你帶回來
This ain't no furniture warehouse, man.
這不是家具倉庫 伙計
I don't do no credit.
我可不做“公益活動”
Get the fuck out of here before I decide to get off my couch, man.
在我決定從沙發上起來前給我滾
Yo, who's this fool pulling up?
朝我們開過來的傻子是誰
Oh, shit!
見鬼
Crazy motherfucker.
混蛋瘋子
Cocaine, Oxy, meth. Full service dealer.
可卡因 氧可酮 冰毒 各種毒品應有盡有
Motherfucker.
你是誰 混蛋
Don't mind me.
別管我是誰
I'll be taking this.
我會拿走這個
And this.
還有這個
For the outreach program.
這是給外展計劃的
Bar codes are perfect.
條形碼很完美
Holograms, bulletproof.
全息圖很立體
Money in the bag? Help yourself.
- 錢在包里  - 請自便
Six-figure instruments are in the front.
六位數儀器在前面
First time I heard about bearer bonds was Beverly Hills Cop.
我第一次聽說無記名債券 是在《比佛利山莊警察》里
I didn't know if they were real or Hollywood bullshit.
我不知道這是真的還是電影里杜撰的
You could shine a lighthouse on 'em, man. Watermarks are flawless.
你可以為他們點亮一座燈塔 水印完好無損
No one'll really know who you really are.
沒人會知道你是誰
But you know.
但你知道
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Just getting back? - Yeah.
- 剛回來  - 是的
Had to go to three stores to get what I needed. You?
我不得不去了三家店 才買到我想要的東西 你呢
Got everything I needed in one place. Bet you did.
- 一個地方就搞定了我要的所有東西 - 那可真好
Oh, shit.
見鬼
See you're still using brass knuckles.
我看到你還在用銅指虎
No more switchblade?
不用彈簧刀了
Look down.
往下看
Hey, O'Donnell.
嘿 奧唐納
Hey, Neagley.
嘿 內格利
Don't blame me for this shithole. I found it like this.
別指責我弄亂了房間 我發現時已經成這樣了
I was with my family.
我當時跟我家人在一起
It was, uh, Unplugged Week.
那周是不插電周
That sounds awful.
聽起來很可怕
No shit.
可不是嘛
Once a year, my wife makes us get a cabin in the middle of nowhere,
每年一次 我老婆給我們 在一個偏僻的地方租了一間小屋
no cell phones, no devices, no TVs.
沒有手機 沒有設備 沒有電視
Less screens, more greens.
遠離屏幕 親近自然
Good in theory, till by the third day my devil children want to kill each other.
理論上很好 但到了第三天 我的惡魔孩子們就想互相殘殺
So, I got home, checked the voice mail, got here as quick as I could.
我回到家 檢查了語音信箱 盡快趕到了這里
Assholes snapped my toothbrush in half.
那混蛋把我的牙刷折成了兩半
Now I own nothing.
現在我一無所有了
Glad to see you haven't changed.
很高興你沒變
You have.
你變了
Family vacations. Wife telling you what to do.
家庭度假 老婆奴
Not the oversexed degenerate I remember.
不是我記憶中性欲過剩的墮落者了
I've been domesticated.
我被馴化了
Apparently.
顯然是的
Got to say, pretty pissed about this whole Franzy thing.
我得說 弗朗茨的事讓我很生氣
Kind of loved that kid.
我很愛那孩子
So... who we killing over it?
所以我們要殺誰呢
When are you due back on the catwalk?
你什么時候重回T臺了
God, you must've been mortified when you saw
你看到你穿著跟那個無家可歸的
you were wearing the same clothes as the homeless guy taking a shit in a coffee can out back.
在后面的咖啡罐里拉屎的人 一樣的衣服一定覺得很羞愧吧
Shit. Password protected.
見鬼 密碼保護
Hate guessing passwords. About to hate it more.
- 我討厭猜密碼 - 即將更討厭猜
Franz set it up so we get three guesses in two minutes or the drive's erased.
它已經設置好了 所以我們得在 兩分鐘內試三次 否則U盤會被刪除
And it auto-launched once it recognized a new device.
它會隨著新設備自動啟動
- You got to be shitting me. - Nope.
- 你在搞我吧 - 沒
Okay, so we got to break Franzy down like we'd profile a perp.
所以我們要像分析罪犯一樣 分析弗朗茨
Passwords come from deep down.
密碼來自于內心深處
What was Franzy's thing? What was he known for?
弗朗茨的特點是什么  他因什么而出名
Being smart. Yeah, but we were all pretty smart.
- 因聰明而出名 - 是啊 但我們都很聰明
Pittsburgh? That's all the guy talked about.
匹茲堡 他總說起那里
Pirates, Steelers, that, uh, that sandwich place where they put the fries on top.
海盜隊 鋼人隊 那家把薯條放在面上的三明治店
- Primanti Brothers. - That was it.
- 普利曼迪兄弟 - 對
Yeah, but not Pittsburgh in and of itself. It was his loyalty to it.
不是匹茲堡本身 是他對它的忠誠
Franz was a loyal guy.
弗朗茨是個忠誠的人
Still loved the 110th after all these years, taught his kid our slogan.
這么多年來一直很喜歡110組 他還教他的孩子們我們的口號
Do you remember when he used to claim
記得他聲稱1979年的海盜隊
that the Pirates of '79 were better than the Yankees of '78?
比1978年的洋基隊更好
I mean, the little shit wasn't even alive when those teams played and he'd still argue his ass off.
他們比賽的時候 他都還沒出生呢 而他還在那兒吵
Okay, but loyalty is a byproduct. Where does it come from?
但忠誠是個副產品 忠誠從何而來
Hero worship. Respect.
英雄崇拜 尊重
If Franz respected someone, he couldn't be dissuaded.
如果他尊重一個人 他就不會被旁人所左右
Pirates were the greatest team ever. Miles Davis was the greatest musician ever.
海盜隊是最厲害的隊伍 邁爾斯戴維斯是最偉大的音樂家
Franz was loyal to what he respected. That's it. You got it.
- 弗朗茨忠于他尊重的人和事 - 就是這個 你說對了
Roberto Clemente.
羅伯特克萊門特
He'd only use the last name.
他會只用姓氏
Wait! What about Willie Stargell?
等等 威利斯塔格爾呢
Did Willie Stargell die in a plane crash delivering supplies to earthquake victims?
威利斯塔格爾在給地震災民 運送物資時死于飛機失事嗎
It's Clemente.
是克萊門特
No, it isn't.
不 不是
Who would use a device like this? Franz. For this very reason.
- 誰會用這種設備  - 弗朗茨 正是因為這個原因
I'm gonna try Miles Davis. Franz worshipped the guy.
我會試試邁爾斯戴維斯 弗朗茨很崇拜這家伙
Good a guess as any. Go for it.
很好的猜測 大膽試試吧
Nope. Shit.
- 不對 - 見鬼
This is why I hate guessing passwords.
這就是為何我討厭猜密碼
Oh, this makes me sick to even suggest this,
我很不想提出這個建議
and outside of this room I'll deny ever saying it,
走出這個房間 我會否認這種說法
but who did Franz respect more than anyone? Any ballplayer, any artist?
但比起任何球員 藝術家 他最尊重的人是誰
Who did he hero worship?
他崇拜的英雄是誰
Get the hell out of here.
別添亂
A few weeks into the 110th, the kid started cutting his hair like you,
進入110組的前幾周 他剪了跟你一樣的發型
talking like you, following you around. He wanted to be you, Reacher.
像你一樣說話 跟著你 他想成為你
You better punch that. We're running out of time.
最好確認輸入吧 我們時間不多了
Son of a bitch.
王八蛋
Don't go getting a big head.
別自以為是
Hello.
你好
Would you like this?
你想要這個嗎
Now, do you know why I love comic books so much?
你知道我為何那么喜歡漫畫書嗎
Because the good guys always win.
因為好人總能獲勝
Mr. McBride? You're booked for your flight to Denver.
麥克布萊德先生 您預訂了飛往丹佛的航班
Enjoy your trip. Thank you. I certainly will.
- 祝您旅途愉快 - 謝謝 一定會愉快的
Andrew McBride. Alan Mason. Alejandro Mendez. Alexander Markopoulos.
“安德魯麥克布萊德 艾倫梅森 亞歷杭德羅門蒂斯 亞歷山大...”
Just a list of names, all starting with the initials A.M.
只是一個名單 其中所有名字的首字母都是AM
All aliases. You keep the same initials so your signature never has to change.
全是化名 你保留同樣的首字母 這樣你的簽名永遠都不會變
Just an A and an M with a squiggle after it, no matter which pseudonym you're using.
就一個“A”加一個帶波浪線的“M” 無論化名具體是什么
Well, at least you can read yours.
至少你那部分內容還能讀出來
I've just got page after page of random numbers.
我剛得到的是一頁又一頁的隨機數據
No order. No meaning. Nothing. At least to us. For now.
- 沒有順序 沒有意義 什么都沒 - 至少我們覺得沒有 而且暫時而已
Well, whatever this shit is, it was enough to get Franz killed,
無論這是什么 它害死了弗朗茨
your rooms trashed, and God knows whatever else we don't know about.
還害得你們的房間被毀 天知道我們還不知道些什么
These guys aren't shy about getting aggressive.
這些人可不會手軟
We need more manpower. Hate to say it, but he's right.
- 我們需要更多人力 - 我不愿承認 但他說得對
None of the 110th are reachable.
110組的人都聯系不上
Well, we send a Christmas card to Swan every year.
我們每年都給斯旺寄圣誕賀卡
I think he lives in Queens now.
我想他現在住在皇后區
I'll have Lilly check our holiday mailer list.
我會讓莉莉查看我們的假期郵件列表
What? You really are domesticated.
- 怎么了  - 你真的被馴化了
No noise coming from inside. A little New York background music?
里面沒有任何噪音 一點紐約背景音樂
Yo, Carlo! Your mom says you got to be home for dinner!
卡洛 你媽說你得回家吃飯
Oh. You smell that?
你們聞到了嗎
I'll take the upstairs.
我去樓上
In here.
在這里
Collar says Maisi.
頸圈上寫著:“麥絲”
Drank the toilet bowl dry.
它把馬桶水喝干了
Dehydration. That's a tough way to die.
脫水而亡 這種死法太痛苦了
Swan would never let a dog die of thirst.
斯旺永遠不會讓狗渴死
The only way he doesn't come home is if he couldn't come home.
如果他不回家 那只有一種可能
Swan's dead.
斯旺死了
Franzy, now Swan...
先是弗朗茨 現在是斯旺
We can't get ahold of the other team members, either.
我們也聯系不上團隊其他成員
Boss?
老大
What are you thinking?
你有什么想法
Major?
少校
I'm thinking there's someone hellbent on taking out the Special Investigators.
我覺得有人一心想干掉特別調查員
And they're coming after us.
他們是沖我們來的
Good.
很好